<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[TableLess]]></title>
  <link href="http://tableless-ui.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://tableless-ui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-07T11:13:46-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://tableless-ui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Austin Dick and Isaac Hunter]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Spiritual Gifts [Dummy Text]]]></title>
    <link href="http://tableless-ui.github.io/blog/2014/03/07/whatisuiux/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-07T17:55:03-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tableless-ui.github.io/blog/2014/03/07/whatisuiux</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The first is <strong>wisdom</strong>. This is in <em>1 Corinthians 12:8</em>. Okay, if you have this gift, you love giving timely, helpful insight. You can read people and circumstances, and everybody’s looking at it like a knot. They’re like, “How do we untie this knot? I don’t understand what we—” and you say, “Okay, how about this? How about that? Let me explain.” And you say the truth. You give wise insight, and everybody’s like, “That’s it!” This can be organizationally. This can be interpersonally. What you don’t need is counsel; you need wise counsel. Alright, the world isn’t lacking in counsel, right? It’s lacking in wise counsel. Some of you are looking for advice. Make sure you go to a wise source. People with the gift of wisdom are a great gift.</p>

<p>The gift of <strong>knowledge</strong>—<em>1 Corinthians 12:8</em>. Okay, if you have this gift, you love to study. You love to research, alright. “Love the Lord your God with all your mind—” you’re like, “I will.” You love that. You might like books and footnotes and dead people. You love that. You love that. If somebody comes up to you, and they’re like, “Have you ever studied?” You’re like, “Oh yes, I have, and I thought that perhaps that nerdy joy would never be used, and I am so glad that you have showed up to talk to me about the difference between Barth and Berkhof, and I’m ready.” Okay, you’re—now, the rest of you don’t even know what I’m talking about, but the nerds, I just spoke their love language, okay? You love to research. You love to study. I’ve got a pretty significant knowledge/nerd side. I’ve got a huge library. I’ve got a lot of books on my laptop. I like books, I like to look at them, I like to have them around. They’re like friends, right? I like to study, I like to think, I’m more of an introvert, I like the life of the mind. Okay, it’s a gift of knowledge. Some of you have that. Those of you that love this, you love it when people come up to you, they’re like, “Can I ask you a question?” You’re like, “Yes, you can, anytime!” You’re very excited. If somebody says, “Do you have a good book for me?” you’re like, “Yes, a stack of extra ones, and I will give you one of them. I was hoping someone would ask.” Okay, gift of knowledge.</p>

<p>Gift of <strong>faith</strong>. Okay, if you have the gift of faith—this is <em>1 Corinthians 12:9</em>—you love tough or impossible situations. Other people are like, “That’ll never happen,” you’re like, “Yes, it will.” My wife, Grace, has this gift. She’s big faith girl. She just trusts God. It’s been super helpful in this job, because I’ll come up to her—I’ll be like, “I think we’re supposed to put a waterslide on the moon.” She’ll be like, “Great! So, we’ll pray for a waterslide, an astronaut, and a shuttle. When do you need it by?” I mean, she’s—and she’ll pray, and I’ll get a waterslide, and an astronaut, and a shuttle. And I’ll be like, “It happened.” She’s like, “Of course it happened; we asked for it.” Whoa! Okay, some of you have the gift of faith. You just—you trust God, but it’s not a naïveté; it’s a childlike faith. It’s not a childish faith, but it’s a childlike faith. You’re like, “Well, if God wants it, and he tells us, it’s going to happen.” Some of you have the gift of faith, right? This is the opposite of some of you who have the gift of discouragement. “It’ll never work,” right? You’re like Eeyore. “It’s going to be terrible.” The opposite of that is the gift of faith. You believe things can happen.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
